<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
    <idinfo>
        <citation>
            <citeinfo>
                <title>SNC_Subregions</title>
                <geoform>vector digital data</geoform>
            </citeinfo>
        </citation>
        <descript>
            <abstract>Boundary Sierra Nevada Conservancy (SNC) boundary. The boundary was mapped to correspond with statute AB 2600 (2004) and as re-defined in SB 208 (2022). Work on the boundary was completed by CalFire, GreenInfo Network, and the California Department of Fish and Game. Meets and bounds description of the area as defined in statute: PRC Section 33302 (f) defines the Sierra Nevada Region as the area lying within the Counties of Alpine, Amador, Butte, Calaveras, El Dorado, Fresno, Inyo, Kern, Lassen, Madera, Mariposa, Modoc, Mono, Nevada, Placer, Plumas, Shasta, Sierra, Siskiyou, Tehama, Trinity, Tulare, Tuolumne, and Yuba, described as the area bounded as follows: On the east by the eastern boundary of the State of California; the crest of the White/Inyo ranges; and State Routes 395 and 14 south of Olancha; on the south by State Route 58, Tehachapi Creek, and Caliente Creek; on the west by the line of 1,250 feet above sea level from Caliente Creek to the Kern/Tulare County line; the lower level of the western slope’s blue oak woodland, from the Kern/Tulare County line to the Sacramento River near the mouth of Seven-Mile Creek north of Red Bluff; the Sacramento River from Seven-Mile Creek north to Cow Creek below Redding; Cow Creek, Little Cow Creek, Dry Creek, and up to the southern boundary of the Pit River watershed where Bear Creek Mountain Road and Dry Creek Road intersect; the southern boundary of the Pit River watershed; the western boundary of the upper Trinity watershed in the County of Trinity; on the north by the boundary of the upper Trinity watershed in the County of Trinity and the upper Sacramento, McCloud, and Pit River watersheds in the County of Siskiyou; and within the County of Modoc, the easterly boundary of the Klamath River watershed; and on the north in the County of Modoc by the northern boundary of the State of California; excluding both of the following: (1) The Lake Tahoe Region, as described in Section 6605.5 of the Government Code, where it is defined as &amp;quot;region&amp;quot; (2) The San Joaquin River Parkway, as described in Section 32510.According to GreenInfo Network and the California Department of Fish and Game, the blue oak woodland used to define a portion of the Sierra Nevada Conservancy's western boundary was delineated using referenced vegetation and imagery data.Subregions“Subregions” means the six subregions in which the Sierra Nevada Region is located, described as follows:(1) The northwest Sierra subregion, comprising the Counties of Shasta, Siskiyou, Tehama, and Trinity.(2) The northeast Sierra subregion, comprising the Counties of Lassen, Modoc, Plumas, and Sierra.(3) The north central Sierra subregion, comprising the Counties of Butte, Nevada, Placer, and Yuba.(4) The south central Sierra subregion, comprising the Counties of Amador, Calaveras, El Dorado, and Tuolumne.(5) The southeast Sierra subregion, comprising the Counties of Alpine, Inyo, Kern, and Mono.(6) The southwest Sierra subregion, comprising the Counties of Fresno, Madera, Mariposa, and Tulare.</abstract>
            <purpose>This feature layer contains the Sierra Nevada Conservacy's subregions which is taking effect January 1, 2024.</purpose>
        </descript>
        <keywords>
            <theme>
                <themekt>None</themekt>
                <themekey>SNC</themekey>
                <themekey>Subregions</themekey>
                <themekey>Sierra Nevada Conservancy</themekey>
                <themekey>Boundary</themekey>
                <themekey>CAOpenData</themekey>
            </theme>
        </keywords>
        <accconst>None</accconst>
        <useconst>This map was prepared by or for the Sierra Nevada Conservancy (SNC).The map has been posted on this site solely for the purpose of general public information; the viewer should not rely upon the contents of this map for any specific purpose without making independent investigation. The SNC assumes no responsibility for any risk, loss, or liability that may result from the viewer's use of the map.</useconst>
        <datacred/>
        <native>Esri ArcGIS 12.8.0.29751</native>
    </idinfo>
    <spdoinfo>
        <direct>Vector</direct>
        <ptvctinf>
            <sdtsterm>
                <sdtstype>GT-polygon composed of chains</sdtstype>
                <ptvctcnt>0</ptvctcnt>
            </sdtsterm>
        </ptvctinf>
    </spdoinfo>
    <eainfo>
        <detailed>
            <enttyp>
                <enttypl>SNC_Subregions</enttypl>
            </enttyp>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl>
                <attrdef>Internal feature number.</attrdef>
                <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
                <attrdomv>
                                        
                    <udom>Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
                                    
                </attrdomv>
            </attr>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>Shape</attrlabl>
                <attrdef>Feature geometry.</attrdef>
                <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
                <attrdomv>
                                        
                    <udom>Coordinates defining the features.</udom>
                                    
                </attrdomv>
            </attr>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>FUNCSTAT</attrlabl>
            </attr>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>Shape_Length</attrlabl>
                <attrdef>Length of feature in internal units.</attrdef>
                <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
                <attrdomv>
                                        
                    <udom>Positive real numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
                                    
                </attrdomv>
            </attr>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>Shape_Area</attrlabl>
                <attrdef>Area of feature in internal units squared.</attrdef>
                <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
                <attrdomv>
                                        
                    <udom>Positive real numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
                                    
                </attrdomv>
            </attr>
        </detailed>
    </eainfo>
    <metainfo>
        <metd>20220913</metd>
        <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
        <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
        <mettc>local time</mettc>
    </metainfo>
</metadata>
